VARUN SONI Digital Marketing Manager

Profile:

Experience Digital Marketina Manager with extensive experience building, maintaining, and running successful digital marketing campaigns. Bringing forth broad marketing knowledge, coupled with focused campaign experience. Adept at creating and implementing client-centered, successful campaigns, aimed at improving brand awareness and presence. Collaborative and creative manager accomplished at managing digital marketing presence content. Experienced in leading teams of marketing professionals to meet and exceed digital marketing goals.

Contact

PHONE:

+91-9898 78 5656

WEBSITE:

www.Amerejuve.com

www.MDofficeManager.com

www.SaveMaxResources.ca

www.KumarWorld.com

www.Kaybeebio.com

EMAIL:

Varunsoni911@gmail.com

EDUCATION:

Master Of Computer Applications.

Aug. 2012 - Jul. 2015

T.John College - Bangalore

Bachelor of Computer Applications.

Jun. 2009 – Jun. 2012

Chimanbhai Patel Institute Of Computer Application – Ahmedabad

P.U.C

May. 2008 - March. 2009

Gyanjyot Vidyalaya – Ahmedabad

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Kay Bee Bio - Digital Marketing Manager

06/2024 - Present (Pune)

- Research and track consumer behaviors and trends
- Planning and managing social media platforms and WhatsApp Marketing.
- Optimize content for the website and social media platforms.
- Manage and Maintain 5 websites WordPress
- Overseeing and managing all contests, giveaways, and other digital projects.
- Work with the marketing team to brainstorm new strategies and technique.
- Researched keywords relevant to marketing efforts of agriculture.

Kumar World - Digital Marketing Manager

09/2022-05/2024 (Pune)

Developing and monitoring campaign budgets.

Course

Digital Marketing at National Institute Of Digital Marketing -Bangalore

- Manage relationships with agencies, vendors, and other third parties
- Identifying the latest trends and technologies affecting our industry.
- Evaluating important metrics that affect our website traffic, service quotas, and target audience.
- Overseeing and managing all contests, giveaways, and other digital projects.
- Developed unique content for a variety of clients sites to improve presence and brand awareness.
- Researched keywords relevant to marketing efforts of clients.

Crystal Voxx - Digital Marketing Specialist

04/2018-08/2022 (Ahmedabad)

- Coordinated mailings, marketing materials, and website content.
- Generated invigorating social media content.
- Email Marketing Trumpia & MailChimp
- Worked alongside marketing specialists and graphic designers.
- Scale campaigns to maximize ROI
- Monitor social media and Google Analytics
- Optimize paid advertising campaigns using SEO and other tools

Masira DM Pvt. Ltd. - Digital Marketing Executive 03/2017–04/2018 (Bangalore)

- Provide creative ideas for content marketing and update website
- Collaborate with designers to improve user experience
- Acquire insight in online marketing trends and keep strategies up-to-date
- Be actively involved in SEO efforts (keyword, image optimization etc.)

- Maintain partnerships with media agencies and vendors
- Prepare online newsletters and promotional emails.

SKILLS

